ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
EDEN ACADEMY UNIFORM SHOP
99.5…
Anya has grown two millimeters
since the last time!
It must be a margin of error.
Maybe not.
Children grow so fast.
That's right.
Then, should we have them made
a little bigger so she can grow into them?
I still can't believe
that you were already married, Yor!
You should've told me the last time
you two were in here together.
I'm sorry about the other day…
And your daughter was accepted into
the prestigious Eden Academy!
Congratulations!
Thanks!
Are you an alumni of Eden as well, sir?
No, I'm a third-rate countryside graduate…
Oh, then you must be careful.
Eden is a long established school,
so there’s a bit of a wall
between the alumni and the non-alumni,
and that seems to breed discrimination
and bullying among the kids.
There are other problems,
like privileged students being arrogant
and the discord between
the boarders and day students…
Speaking of day students, kidnapping
seems to be a frequent occurrence.
Probably because only wealthy families
can afford to go to Eden.
Anya doesn't want to go to school anymore.
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
There are lots of fun things too,
so don't worry.
Okay, the measurements are done.
So, your purchases are
one full uniform set,
one winter coat, a vest, a sweater,
and three other items.
We'll have it ready for you quickly
since you're a regular.
Other designated items are available
at the store on the corner.
This costs a lot of money…
What's wrong?
I'm scared of being kidnapped.
I see. You're thinking too far ahead.
Yor, do you mind if we eat out today?
Not at all.
There won't be any kidnappers
at the restaurant?
Here is today's special.
Sautéed pork with
papaw sauce and porcini on the side
and potato potage.
Huh?
Looks delicious.
It must be the P code.
They're contacting me for a briefing.
In five days' time at 1 p.m.,
at safehouse D.
Understood.
But I need them to stop
contacting me this way. I don't like it.
FIVE DAYS LATER
Hello? Oh, hello.
-It's finished already?
-Huh?
Okay. I'll come by to pick it up. See you.
The uniform is ready?
Seems to be.
However, I have a briefing today.
Can I ask you to go with Anya?
I have some work I need to attend to.
Of course. Leave it to me.
I might be late,
so feel free to order takeout.
-Okay.
-Have a good day!
Hello, or should I say, good evening,
Agent Twilight.
Hey, Handler. What is it?
Before that…
What was that big expense the other day!
Castle rental
and palace furniture rentals!
How much money do you think we have?!
Here's an additional bill.
Admission requires a lot of things.
You have the guts to
give it to me so casually.
Both were necessary.
Fine.
Today we're checking in on
the progress of Operation Strix Phase Two.
You may not need this
since you're a very thorough person.
Well…
I've been letting things
unfold as they go lately, so…
Phase Two. Social gathering.
For this explanation,
let's review the Eden system.
Eden College.
There are approximately 2,500 students.
There are 13 grades in total
and students range from ages six to 19.
Academics. Sports. Arts.
They're the top-ranked institution
in all subjects.
The best and the brightest
at this elite school
are honors students
called Imperial Scholars.
In order to attend the reception
to which Desmond belongs,
you must be a parent of
one of these Imperial Scholars.
To be selected as an honors student,
a student must obtain
eight medals of merit, known as Stellas.
Stellas are awarded for outstanding grades
and contributions to society.
In other words, you first have to raise
your daughter to be an honors student.
You may use foul means if necessary.
On the other hand,
there is a penalty called
Tonito for poor grades and misbehavior.
Be careful because if you accumulate eight
of these, you'll be expelled immediately.
-Now the meeting regarding our plan…
-To make her an honors student…
I only have doubts in my mind.
Does Anya look cute in her uniform?
Yes, very cute! Very cute!
Let's go to the photo studio later!
Is Anya cute?
Yes, very cute! Very cute!
Can they go home already?
How many times do they have to do this?
Anya wants to go out like this!
Let's do it!
Thank you!
Shall we stop by the park?
This is Anya's uniform! Ta-da!
This is Anya in her uniform! Ta-da!
What a cute child you have!
She's a student at Eden? I envy you!
Hello.
Mommy, I'm hungry!
What shall we do for dinner?
Hamburger steak!
You want your previous mommy!
I want to be with them forever.
I know that we're a fake family.
But I wonder
how I can be more motherly to her.
Mother!
I showed everyone how cute Anya is!
You can't get your uniform dirty
before school starts!
Say, Anya. Shall we stop by
the supermarket on the way home?
Hm?
Loid said he'll be late,
so I'll make dinner tonight!
Oh! Mother, can you cook?
Yes! I'll do my best!
-Hey, is that a student from Eden?
-Huh?
-Is that woman her mother?
-Must be a nanny!
A rich woman would never shop for herself.
I feel like I want some allowance.
Me too.
As long as I have some meat and vegetables
I'll be able to make something.
I don't know what's what,
so I'll just buy one of each!
Ta-da!
-Anya's bored so she's going out first!
-Don't go far!
Hey, little girl.
Be a good girl for just a moment.
We'll let you go as soon as
we get some money from your nanny.
Bad guys!
Eden has bullying and kidnapping…
It was true!
I heard we can sell their uniforms
for a good amount too!
How awesome! Then, little girl--
What… are you doing?
Oh, now you'll have to pay us
medical expenses too!
Show us your wallet, nanny.
I've spent all my money,
so I don't have anything.
So, please, go home.
I see. Then we'll be finished
once we take her uniform.
You'll be fired anyway,
so go back to the countryside
where you came from, you little maid!
Th… The pumpkin… with her bare hands?!
I'm that girl's mother!
Get out of here,
unless you want to end up
like that vegetable!
Mother…
Are you okay?
I'm sorry… I shouldn't have
let you out of my sight! There, there.
I've wasted all this food…
I'm such an awful mother…
Anya likes her mother
who's strong and cool! There, there.
Special punch! Bam!
How embarrassing!
Mother!
Train Anya!
T… Train?
I now know that Eden students
face a lot of danger.
But if I train and become strong,
I'll be a little less scared.
I'll be able to do my best in school
without dying!
Anya wants to be like Mother!
Even if I can't be like a normal mother,
I'll do my best with everything I can do!
Okay, then we'll start training
as soon as we get home!
Training!
I'm home!
-Yah! Yah!
-Hm?
What are you doing?
Preparing for school!
Yah!
-Uh…
-Yah!
-My head is seriously filled with doubt…
You are the chosen ones!
Congratulations to
the 228 students
who have successfully passed through
the narrow gate of Eden,
and are here today,
due to their own efforts
or those of their parents or guardians.
We at Eden Academy
extend a hearty welcome to you!
We've finally made it this far.
Father, there's a lot of people
with the same clothes as me!
Yes, that's what a uniform is.
We still have a lot of problems, but…
Listen, Twilight.
There is a condition to attend
the social gathering with Desmond.
The student must be
elected as an Imperial Scholar.
To do so, she must be
at the top of her class in many subjects.
Don't forget that
the future of the East and West
depends on this operation.
Making her an elite…
But I've already given up on that.
What?!
It's difficult as it is to maintain
the top position in this school
which only has the best
and the brightest students. Rather…
Next, I will announce the class divisions
and homeroom teachers.
Please come forward when you're called.
Class One. Specter House. William Howard.
Theodore Russell.
Grace Fayne. Jessica Clarke.
-Next, Class Two.
-I wonder what class Anya will be in.
-We'll see.
-Lucy Gallen.
No, I already know.
Because I falsified some information to
make it more convenient for the mission.
Alice Paullette.
-So Anya will be…
-Edward Workshire.
-Damian Desmond.
-…in the same class as him.
Target Donovan Desmond's
second son, Damian.
He should've added "Mr." to the title!
Enrolled in Eden following the eldest son.
I marked him the moment I found
his name on the list of applicants.
Jesse Capel.
In case our Plan A of becoming
an honors student doesn't work out,
we have Plan B.
The Friendship Strategy!
One. Be in the same class
and become friends with him.
Two. Both of us will get
invited to his house for a play date.
Three. Direct contact with the target!
I'm sure it won't be that easy,
but it's good to have backup plans.
-Anya Forger.
-Ah!
Go ahead.
Anya has lived with children her age
at the orphanage for a long time.
Let's believe in her communication skills.
The bad boss's kid.
What's with that girl?
Has she already noticed my charm,
and fallen in love with me?
She has a good eye.
She must be shy. How cute.
Becky Blackbell.
Burp.
Nice to meet you!
That's…
the daughter of CEO Blackbell,
a major military company!
Behind her is the family member
of the People's Assembly!
That's the son of
a key figure in the Security Service!
Her classmates are
a treasure trove of information!
Get along with all of them, Anya!
Loid is always so passionate
when it comes to his child.
I'm Becky! What about you?
She's so childish.
I guess I can use her to take care of me.
-Hmph!
-Huh?
Hey!
The homeroom teacher is Mr. Henderson.
-Oh.
-Oh, the nice teacher!
I guess he was spared from being fired.
It seems unfair that the house master
is in charge of the elementary students,
but he's lucky that's
the only punishment he got.
I'll go back to basics
and give them a good shake.
Now, new students will tour the school
with their homeroom teachers
and then go to their classrooms.
In the meantime,
parents are welcome to wait
and socialize in the lounge at Building C.
Good luck, Anya.
Starting now, it's up to you.
Okey dokey.
Hey, you! Keep pace with everyone!
I'm so worried…
It's difficult to send them off, isn't it?
I understand.
This is the dining room.
A first-class chef serves
elegant dishes every day.
There is also
a special dining room in the back,
which is only open to Imperial Scholars.
Anyone with an elegant academic record
and eight Stellas can become a Scholar.
Everyone is encouraged to
devote themselves to it.
Yes!
On the other hand, if you're a failure,
you'll be punished or expelled depending
on the number of Tonitos you have.
Why is he looking at Anya?
Mr. Damian,
you'll be a Scholar in no time!
Of course.
Right!
I'm the son of
the president of the National Unity Party.
-Wow!
-Really?
My father said that we're
indebted to the Desmond group!
Hey! Stop with the chit-chat!
How stupid!
How about you? What do your parents do?
Depending on your status,
I can let you be my friend.
Anya has to be patient for the mission.
Sp-- A psychiatrist.
Huh, that's nothing special.
Your parents probably only have
crappy assets. How lame.
Anya wants to go play at your house!
Don't be stupid! Know your place, ugly!
Common people are
really brazen, aren't they?
Get out of here
before you spread your commoner germs!
Now is the time to do my special punch!
Listen carefully, Anya.
Those who wield power
by letting their emotions
get the better of them
are not truly strong.
You'll be a cool lady if you can laugh off
some light bullying.
A lady?!
Also, if you keep smiling,
a fight won't occur.
You're so pathetic! Fight back!
Anya doesn't care one bit.
Why is she laughing at and mocking me?
Maturity! She's so mature, like an adult!
I was mistaken to have thought
she was childish!
You are surprisingly mature!
I'm starting to see you in a new light!
Mature?
Don't get carried away, you ugly duck!
Ugly, ugly, ugly!
Mr. Damian…
Maybe you should watch your vocabulary…
What's with you? Yes, she's uglier than
me, but you don't have to go that far!
Shut up!
You there! How many times have I told you?
Do you want to be punished
on your first day?
Damn her! Making a fool of me
on the first day! I'll never forgive her!
Mother's a liar. Smiling isn't working.
I'm going to tell the teacher
if you don't cut it out!
Do you have proof that we did it?
-That's right!
Move!
Hey, smiling freak.
I'm going to bully the crap
out of you from now on.
I'm going to bully you so bad
that you'll never be able to smile!
Even if you make her cry,
her psychiatrist daddy might fix her!
-Seriously? That'd be hilarious!
-Good for you!
Hey! Where are you looking?
Are you scared now, or what?
What's all the commotion?
Teacher! She punched Mr. Damian!
I just stretched my arms
and he was standing there.
Liar! Do you think you can
talk your way out of this?!
In fact, you checked whether
the teacher was looking or not!
Do you have proof that Anya did it?
Your handprint is right here!
Lying is a shameful act,
Anya Forger!
No, Teacher!
She was being so patient the entire time,
but these guys…
But is it true that you punched him?
Listen carefully, Anya.
The right time to use your strength is,
for example,
when helping your friend out of trouble.
Her foot.
He was stepping on it,
so Anya got mad. I'm sorry.
For me?! Anya!
-She has the spirit to contain her
-Thank you!
-personal resentment, but she stands up
-Thank you, Anya!
to the boys for the sake of her friends!
How elegant, Anya Forger.
However…
Just as I expected,
neither Desmond nor his wife showed up.
I guess I don't need to rush it.
Now that we're in,
-Guardians!
-we have plenty of time.
-I was able to expand my network too.
-The students finished their orientation,
-…so please head to the courtyard.
-Come this way!
-We'll take a group photo together.
-Where's Anya?
Forger. Come with me.
She punched a boy?!
Are you hurt?
-To top it off, it's Desmond's son… Why?
-Normally, she would get three Tonitos
…for violence without question,
but at my discretion,
I decided to make it only one.
I will make no further concessions.
I'm sorry, Loid!
It's all because I trained her!
I'll tell his parents as well.
She lost a point on the first day here.
And to top it off, her relationship
with Damian just went down the drain.
Okay, everyone!
We're going to take the picture!
The family in the right corner,
smile more!
Say "cheese"!
TO BECOME AN HONORS STUDENT: 8 MORE STARS
TO BE EXPELLED: 7 MORE STARS
RELATIONSHIP WITH DAMIAN: -100
MISSION:7 TARGET: THE SECOND SON
Subtitle translation by: Nana Onishi